meet Mr Verma the head accountant of a
leading private school the Pearl High
School like every year the schools have
reopened and as usual parents have lined
up to pay the school fees at counters
this situation occurs every first week
of the month which leaves Mr Verma super
stressed from ensuring error fee
collection of fees to cash management to
staff salary payments vendor payments
and Reconciliation
Mr Verma and his team faces a tough time
every single month the exhaustive
paperwork leads to stress chaos and
confusion in Mr verma's team but we at
ICICI Bank have the right solution to
simplify their banking problems ICI Bank
presents customized digital payment
solutions for educational
institutions here's what we offer for
smoother and hassle-free fee collection
process easy app easy pay a One-Stop
solution for a smooth and convenient
payment option for students and parents
via various online and offline
Channels with easy pay you can get
faster credit of funds customize Mis
reports for all modes build capacity to
integrate easily with client Erp System
card swiping terminal UPI /qr code
parents can scan the QR code and easily
make the required payment via any UPI
enabled app we understand that along
with collection of fees an educational
institute has to manage timely payments
to multiple stakeholders like staff
teachers vendors Etc introducing our
One-Stop payment solution ICICI Bank IM
multipay IM multipay is a bulk
disbursement solution for making payment
to Associated stakeholders in electronic
and physical mode through a single file
upload IM multipay provides payment
intimation to beneficiary through mail
or
SMS Consolidated Mis and login dashboard
to institutes apart from collection and
Payment Solutions we also provide an
Enterprise solution to institutions
through our partners that manage
operations of fee collection accept
online payment and maintain Financial
records of the institution through the
platform parents can easily access the
student records and pay fees anytime
through the app or web portal the
platform provides 24x7 web portal for
institution admin for Day to-day
Management with ICI Bank Solutions Mr
Burma of the Pearl High School is now
digitally empowered and saves a lot of
time money and effort on the financial
management of the school for most more
information please contact our
relationship manager or visit your
nearest ICI Bank branch
[Music]